Guide to the A Gathering of the Tribes Records MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Audiovisual Recordings, 1983-2011; 13 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 unknown profile containers, and 4 items in a shared cassette box.; 18.99 Gigabytes in 11 computer files; 305 items on audio and video carriers.
  - Subseries I.B. Audio, 1992-1998
    - Blood Work, by Michael Connelly, 1998; ID: 198.0285; 5 media elements 5 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 15:00:00; Original Format: Audiocassettes (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0285)
    - The Inferno, of Dante, 1998; ID: 198.0295; 4 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 06:00:00; Original Format: Audiocassette (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0295)
    - Gaudi's Show -- Dan Cameron, George Longfish, Sharp, Robert Colescott, undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 198.0302)
    - Gaudi's Show -- Ida Applebroog, undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 198.0303)
    - Gaudi's Show -- Lee Quiñones, Daze, Wendy Olsoff, undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 198.304)
    - Gaudi's Show -- Arnaldo Roche, undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 198.305)
    - Unknown Band Performance, undated; cuid40329 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_7)
- Series II. Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks, 1992-2014; 6 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 2 unknown profile containers.
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  This series contains scrapbooks and photograph albums dating from 1992 to 2014 that were created and maintained by A Gathering of the Tribes staff and volunteers. These scrapbooks and albums document events, gallery openings, readings, and performances through photographs, promotional material, press clippings, and other ephemera.
  - Scrapbook, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1992-2001 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook Loose Items -- Clippings, Photographs, Announcements, 1994-1998 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Photograph Album -- Events and Openings, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Binder 12)
  - Scrapbook -- Events, Openings, 1995-2005 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1997 (Box 23, Binder 12)
  - Scrapbook -- Gallery Events, 1997-2001 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1998 (Box 23, Binder 13)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 23, Binder 13)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Binder 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Binder 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Binder 15)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2014 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Binder 15)
  - Photograph Album -- Events and Openings, circa 2000-2009 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
  - Photograph Album -- Events and Openings, 2000s (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Binder 16)
  - Photograph Album -- Events and Openings, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Item 5, Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Photograph Albums -- Events and Openings, 2004-2005 (Box 40, Folder 3-5)
  - Scrapbook -- Lisa Fittipaldi Exhibition Opening, September 8, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Photograph Albums -- Events and Openings, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 7-9)
  - Scrapbook -- Events, Openings, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album -- Events and Openings, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photograph Albums -- Events and Openings, undated (Box 41, Folder 3-6)
  - Photograph Albums -- Events and Openings, undated (Box 41, Folder 7, Box 42, Folder 1-9, Box 43, Folder 1)
- Series III. Project Files, 1983-2019; 12 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize flat boxes, 1 record carton, 1 small flat box, 1 flat-file folder, 18 digital carriers in two shared boxes, and 3 containers with unknown profiles.
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by file title.
  This series contains files created by A Gathering of the Tribes for the operation of their gallery, performance space, magazine, and the imprint, Fly By Night Press. This series contains administrative files including an organizational history, by-laws, press clippings, and correspondence. Exhibition files and lists are in this series, as well as artist submission packets sent from those who have exhibited or wished to exhibit in the Tribes gallery space. Artist packets typically contain bios sheets, resumes, exhibit catalogs, and artwork images. Promotional material and event calendars date from 1995 to 2013, and are complemented by guest books and files for individual events, including the Charlie Parker Festival. Fly By Night Press files include royalty statements, writer submissions, mockups for the publication Catweazle NYC, and files related to Anyssa Kim and the publishing of her 2003 book Ovarian Twists: New and Selected Poems. Files related to the publication A Gathering of the Tribes include cover designs, layouts for issues #7-9, writer submissions, as well as mock-ups and page layouts for the 10th anniversary edition.
  - America Too, by LaVerne Williams, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Arnaldo Roche Interview Transcript, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Art Auction, Summer 2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Art Contest, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Articles, 1995-2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Artist File -- Beabout, Leah, 1992-2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Artist File -- Carin, Rosemarie, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Artist File -- Coppola, Jeri, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Artist File -- Dana, Richard, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Artist File -- Holton, Curlee Raven, 1992-2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Artist File -- Johnson, Kathryn Jill, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Artist File -- Kellerman, Moritz, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Artist File -- Lonidier, Fred, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Artist File -- Lowen, Ralph, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Artist File -- McFalls, Michael, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Artist File -- Qualls, Jessica, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Artist File -- Quisgard, Liz Whitney, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Artist File -- Shirami, Ganna, circa 2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Artist File -- Tracy, Kathlene, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Artist File -- Twomey, Chris, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Artist File -- Valeria, Angela, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Artists Submission Packets, 1999-2011 (Box 26, Folder 13-15, Box 27, Folder 1-5)
  - Artists Who Showed at Tribes -- List, January 2004 - June 2005 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Auction, July 2005 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Axel, Bret, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Barnum and Buddha's Poetry Circus, March 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Beatty, Paul, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Benson, Tish, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bishara, Rana, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Blackburn, Bob, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bloom, Randy, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bradley, Peter, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - A Brief History of Tribes, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Calendars and Press Releases, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Charles Gayle Gala, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Charlie Parker Festival, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Charlie Parker Festival, 2000-2008 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Charlie Parker Festival, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Chiang, Fay, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Chromatic Cryptology Art Show, March 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Clarke, Kevin, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Coppola, John, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2019 (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Cruz, Victor Hernandez, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Equinox: Collected Poems, by Barbara Chase-Riboud, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - (E)tres, circa 2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Espinoza, Dora, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Events -- Photographs, 1995, undated (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
  - Events -- Photographs, February 2004; cuid40331 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_2)
  - Events -- Strictly for the Birds -- Photographs, August 21, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Events -- NYU Opening Photographs, 2002-07-16; cuid40332 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_3)
  - Events, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Events, March - August 2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Events, September - December 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Events -- Calendars, Promotional Material, and Announcements, 2003-2013, undated (Box 28, Folder 8-10, Box 29, Folder 1-6)
  - Exhibition -- Tenth Anniversary Celebration Artist Agreements, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition -- Andrew Castrucci, Catalog, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition -- Fresh Identities, Artist Applications, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition -- Space Travelers, Images and Promotional Material, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition -- Artists Submissions for Group Show, December 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition -- Paintings of Color, Artists Information, Promotional Material, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition -- The Girleye Show, Promotional Material, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition -- Truth & Fiction Are Not Strangers, Promotional Material, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition -- Food Solo Show, Mija Jung Bryen -- Images, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions -- Announcements, Lists, Artist Information, 2004-2011 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Exhibitions -- Promotional Cards, 1994-2012, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Feuer, Ejlat, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Fly By Night Press -- It's Not About Time, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - Fly By Night Press -- Roger Bonair Agard Book-Related, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Fly By Night Press -- Writer Submissions, 2003, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Fly By Night Press -- Paul Nelson, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Fly By Night Press Royalties Statements -- EMI, 2006-2011 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Fly By Night Press -- ISBN Numbers-Related, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Fly By Night Press -- Catweazle NYC -- Issues, Drafts, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 14, Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Flyers and Postcards, 1997-2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Flyers -- "Junior, We Will Always Remember Your Laughter", undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Forester, Victoria, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Galleri Uten Navn, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Gallery Administrative Receipts and Lists, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Gallery Calendars, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Exhibitions -- Promotional Material, Artwork Images, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Gallery Files (1 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Gallery Files (2 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Gallery Files (3 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Jacket Designs, 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes, Issue #6 Galleys, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- Notes, Items for Issues, 1996, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- Cover Proof for Issue #7, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- Issue #8 Draft, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes, Issue #9 Galleys, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- 10th Anniversary Edition Drafts, Designs, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- 10th Anniversary Edition Final Page and Art Layout, 2002-2003; cuid40330 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_1)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Press Package, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- Writer Submissions, 2004-2005, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Magazine -- Issue #12 Mockup, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Gaze, Tim, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Get Off That Alligator!, by Martin Marriott, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Gissen, Linda, 1987-1996 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Goddess City, 1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Gohl, Andrea, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Guest Books, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 6-8, Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Guest Books, 2002, 2013-2014 (Box 44, Folder 1, 5)
  - Hammons, David, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Henderson, David -- Autographed Poem, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Henry, Aaron, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Hoagland, Everett, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Howl! Festival, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Hurricane Katrina Benefit -- Letters, Promotional Material, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - "Iberian Tribes" Catalog, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Inez, Colette, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Nikki, circa 2002 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Kent, Lori, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Kim, Anyssa -- Awards, Consignment-Related, Book Expenses, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - List -- Magazine and Small Book Distributors, 1991-2019 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - The Long Decade: Mor Faye and Ba Rah, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lorenzo Pace Sculpture Unveiling, circa 1983-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Photos removed from VHS ID 198.0209 cassette sleeve.
  - Marsalis, Wynton -- Interview Transcript, 1997; cuid40333 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_4)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Montford, Dan Loudfoot, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Myles, Eileen, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Neumann, Shalom, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New York and African Tapestries, by Juanita Torrence-Thompson, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Notes, Signs, circa 2013 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Olinka, Sharon, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Ovarian Twists, by Anyssa Kim, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Packer, Eve, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Photograph of Musician Chris Anderson at Bradley's, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Photograph -- Steve Cannon and Stoop Writers Group Upstairs at Tribes Gallery, February 1995 (Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1995, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Musicians -- Photocopies, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Posters, 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Posters, 2004-2005, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Poetry Contest, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Poets Info, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Press Booklet, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Press Coverage, 1992-2018 (Box 33, Folder 8, Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Press Release Contacts, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Prison Poster Project, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rabinsky, Deborah, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Radosavljevic, Dunja, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Ranard, John, 1997-2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Reed, Ishmael, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Resumes, circa 2000-2007 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Reyes, Aileen, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Sentis, Mireia, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Shows, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Simmons, Daniel, circa 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Ming, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Submissions, 1998-2003 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Submissions, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Submissions, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Submissions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Submissions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Submissions, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Submissions, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Submissions - For Next Issue, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Submissions - Maybe, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Submissions - Rejected, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Submissions - Yes, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Submissions - A Gathering of the Tribes Issue #9, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Submissions, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Subscriptions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Tong, Michael, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Tribes Art Collection, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Tribes Gallery Flyers, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Twomey, Chris, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Van Dyne, Wolfgang, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Villalobos, Marco, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Wakili, Shekaiba, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Watanabe, Tadashi, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - "Who is the Powerful Ghost", May 6-27 2000 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Writer Edits from Mireia Sentis, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Yung, Susan, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Series IV. Grant Files, 1994-2010; 3 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 1 unknown profile container
  This series is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  This series contains A Gathering of the Tribes files accumulated on individual funding sources dating from 1994 to 2010. Files typically contain correspondence, applications, and status reports.
  - Al Jisser Group, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - American Express Foundation, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - The Andy Warhol Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Andy Warhol Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Andy Warhol Foundations for the Visual Arts, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Annual Finance Report for New York State, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - AT&T Foundation, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Bank of America Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Bessy and Alan D. Cohn Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Bloomberg LP, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Borders Group, Inc., 2005 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Bronx Council on the Arts, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Fund for Authors, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Chernow Fund, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Citibank, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs Challenge, Fiscal Year 01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, February 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, May 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, Fiscal year 02, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs, 2003-2007 (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
  - Commerce Bank, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence -- General, Rejections, Other, 1995, 2003-2013 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - The DeMatteis Family Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Documentary Heritage Program, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth George Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Fan Fox and Leslie R. Samuels Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Ford Foundation, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Arts, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, Inc., 2005 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 2004-2005, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Funding, Acceptance, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Gannett Foundation, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - The Gladys Krieble Delmas Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Golden Rule Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - The Golden Rule Foundation, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Goldman Sachs Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Grant Letters, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Grant Replies List, 2006-2009 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Greenwall Foundation, 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Greenwall Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Greenwall Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - The Gunk Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Henry and Elaine Kaufman Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - HSBC in the Community Foundation, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Jerome Foundation, Fiscal Year 00, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Jerome Foundation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Jerome Foundation, Support & Materials, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Jerome Foundation, Letters of Support, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Jerome Foundation, Fiscal Year 02, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jerome Foundation, Final Report 02, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Jerome Foundation, 2003, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Community Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - JP Morgan Chase, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Lannon Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - The Lauder Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - LEF Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - LEF Foundation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - LEF Foundation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - LEF Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - LEF Foundation, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - The Liman Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lopez, Margarita, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Low Priority Grants, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 2003, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lucent Technologies, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Manhattan Arts Development Fund, Fiscal year 01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Manhattan Borough President, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - The Marc Haas Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Margorita Lopez, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Mary Livingston Griggs/May Griggs Burke Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Meet the Composer, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Mertz Gilmore Foundation, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1996-1998, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 2004, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - New York City Council Expense Member Initiatives, 2005, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts '00 Community Assets, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts - Tech Tap Fiscal Year '01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - New York State Charities Bureau, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Pub Request, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Final Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - General, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Website Request, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Publishing Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - New York State Council on the Arts TA Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Theater Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Writers in Residence, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Pub Request, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - New York State Council on the Arts E-Book Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - New York State Council on the Arts TA Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Tech Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 59)